<AstroObjectEntry xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/xen-42/outer-wilds-new-horizons/main/NewHorizons/Schemas/shiplog_schema.xsd">
  <ID>LANGUAGE_DIMENSTION</ID>

  <!--Entry for the translation lab -->
  <Entry>
    <ID>TRANSLATION_LAB_ENTRY_FC</ID>
    <Name>Translation Lab</Name>
    <Curiosity>DREE</Curiosity>
    <IsCuriosity/>

    <!--Park rumor-->
    <RumorFact>
      <ID>LANGUAGE_LAB_RUMOR_FC</ID>
      <SourceID>DREE_PARK_ENTRY_FC</SourceID>
      <Text>I read that one of the Nomai was studying the alien's language in some sort of lab. It has an entrance near Shattered Hearth, above the park with the big tree.</Text>
    </RumorFact>

    <!--Can't fit ship-->
    <RumorFact>
      <ID>LANGUAGE_SMALL_ENTRANCE_RUMOR_FC</ID>
      <IgnoreMoreToExplore/>
      <Text>The entrance seems to be too small for me to fit my ship.</Text>
    </RumorFact>

    <!--Baby fish in the way-->
    <RumorFact>
      <ID>SMALL_FISH_DISCOVERY_RUMOR_FC</ID>
      <IgnoreMoreToExplore/>
      <Text>There are a bunch of baby anglerfish directly blocking the path to the lab.</Text>
    </RumorFact>

    <!--Should be a bigger way-->
    <RumorFact>
      <ID>LANGUAGE_LARGE_ENTRANCE_RUMOR_FC</ID>
      <SourceID>QUARRY_ENTRY_FC</SourceID>
      <Text>I read that the translation lab has a larger entrance somewhere in Briar's Hollow. A Nomai who needed to find it left a temporary beacon at the lab, which then guided them to the larger entrance.</Text>
    </RumorFact>

    <!--Stupid fishies-->
    <RumorFact>
      <ID>ANGLER_DISTRACTION_RUMOR_FC</ID>
      <SourceID>LANDING_ZONE_ENTRY_FC</SourceID>
      <Text>The Nomai hypothesized that anglerfish might not be able to distinguish between organic and inorganic prey.</Text>
    </RumorFact>

    <!--Fish latched on-->
    <ExploreFact>
      <ID>ANGLER_DISTRACTION_SUCCESS_FACT_FC</ID>
      <IgnoreMoreToExplore/>
      <Text>I was able to get the baby anglerfish to latch onto my ship so that I could get past.</Text>
    </ExploreFact>

    <!--Big fish note-->
    <ExploreFact>
      <ID>STARVED_FISH_FACT_FC</ID>
      <IgnoreMoreToExplore/>
      <Text>One of the Nomai observed a massive anglerfish residing near the translation lab. He theorized that, due to its size, it would starve if the Dree did not continue to feed it.</Text>
    </ExploreFact>

    <!--Entry for the actual translations -->
    <Entry>
      <ID>TRANSLATIONS_ENTRY_FC</ID>
      <Name>Translations</Name>
      <Curiosity>DREE</Curiosity>

      <!--Dree name-->
      <ExploreFact>
        <ID>DREE_NAME_FACT_FC</ID>
        <Text>The Nomai in charge of the translations, Sennetti, determined that the aliens referred to themselves as the Dree.</Text>
      </ExploreFact>

      <!--Ditylum name-->
      <ExploreFact>
        <ID>DITYLUM_NAME_FACT_FC</ID>
        <Text>Sennetti worked heavily with a Dree who referred to himself as Ditylum, who was also the first Dree that the Nomai encountered.</Text>
      </ExploreFact>

      <!--Bramble name-->
      <ExploreFact>
        <ID>BRAMBLE_NAME_FACT_FC</ID>
        <Text>The Dree referred to this whole area as the Deep Bramble, and the plant itself simply as the Bramble.</Text>
      </ExploreFact>

      <!--Druidcraft-->
      <ExploreFact>
        <ID>TRANSLATION_DRUIDCRAFT_FACT_FC</ID>
        <Text>Apparently the Dree are talented in druidcraft, giving them some level of influence over the Bramble.</Text>
      </ExploreFact>

      <!--Dictionary-->
      <ExploreFact>
        <ID>TRANSLATOR_UPGRADE_FACT_FC</ID>
        <Text>My translator was able to download a Dree dictionary that Sennetti translated.</Text>
      </ExploreFact>

      <!--No escape-->
      <ExploreFact>
        <ID>NO_ESCAPE_FACT_FC</ID>
        <Text>The Dree revealed to the Nomai that they did not know of any way to escape the Deep Bramble.</Text>
      </ExploreFact>
    </Entry>
  </Entry>
</AstroObjectEntry>