<NomaiObject xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/xen-42/outer-wilds-new-horizons/main/NewHorizons/Schemas/text_schema.xsd">

	<!--Main NomaiText.Branch-->
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>1</ID>
		<Text>
			OKALIS: One of our new friends actually approached me today, I believe that it was the same individual that I had previously met at this campsite.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>2</ID>
		<ParentID>1</ParentID>
		<Text>
			NESIA: Oh? Did they seem to have any particular reason for doing so?
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>3</ID>
		<ParentID>2</ParentID>
		<Text>
			OKALIS: As a matter of fact, they led me to somewhere quite interesting. Do you know of the wooden knot that lies in the center of this area, the one that leads back in through an infinite loop? They took me through there and, contrary to what normally happens, we arrived in an enclosed space.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>4</ID>
		<ParentID>3</ParentID>
		<Text>
			SENNETTI: How strange, what was the space like?
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>5</ID>
		<ParentID>4</ParentID>
		<Text>
			OKALIS: It seemed to be a completely overgrown entrance to this area. They beckoned me through another node, although I did not follow them through for fear of being unable to find my way back.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>6</ID>
		<ParentID>5</ParentID>
		<Text>
			AZOLLA: If a member of this other species desires for us to follow them, it may be worthwhile to do so. They have demonstrated they are not hostile, and they may know how to escape from this place.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>


	<!--NomaiText.Branch 1-->
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>101</ID>
		<ParentID>3</ParentID>
		<Text>
			NESIA: I have passed through the knot you speak of, but I have never arrived anywhere that sounds similar to what you describe.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>102</ID>
		<ParentID>101</ParentID>
		<Text>
			OKALIS: It confuses me as well, Nesia. I am unsure of how to access that area again.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>103</ID>
		<ParentID>102</ParentID>
		<Text>
			NESIA: I have a hypothesis. I have noted that the hole one uses to enter that central knot lines up with where they will re-enter this larger area. If we can locate the exterior of the enclosure that you speak of, we may be able to find the hole that will lead us into it.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>


	<!--NomaiText.Branch 2-->
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>201</ID>
		<ParentID>5</ParentID>
		<Text>
			I don’t understand your strange language, but I hope that you may know mine. Follow where I lead and find us. It may be only a feeling, but I think that our species are fated to meet.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>202</ID>
		<ParentID>5</ParentID>
		<Text>
			OKALIS: Is this our new friend’s writing? How exciting! Sennetti, are you able to understand what they have said?
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>203</ID>
		<ParentID>202</ParentID>
		<Text>
			SENNETTI: Unfortunately, I will need to analyze it more before I can determine what this text says. Though I can assure you I will begin work on my translation as soon as possible.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<!--Ship log reveals go here-->
</NomaiObject>
