<NomaiObject xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/xen-42/outer-wilds-new-horizons/main/NewHorizons/Schemas/text_schema.xsd">

	<!--Main NomaiText.Branch-->
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>1</ID>
		<Text>
			AZOLLA: Since the heat of this planet does not seem to relent on the surface, it seems inadvisable to establish a permanent residence here. Therefore, I would suggest we simply construct a lab to study the <![CDATA[<color=orange>Eye</color>]]>’s signal.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>2</ID>
		<ParentID>1</ParentID>
		<Text>
			NESIA: I believe I may have found a suitable location for this lab. On another island, I found a cave leading down. It leads into an area filled with gas, but I believe the upper area may be cool enough for our equipment to function correctly given the assistance of environmental regulation.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>3</ID>
		<ParentID>2</ParentID>
		<Text>
			AZOLLA: Very good! We will set up a lab there, after determining how best to contend with the gas.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>


	<!--NomaiText.Branch 1-->
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>101</ID>
		<ParentID>1</ParentID>
		<Text>
			OKALIS: While I know the signal is our main focus, I believe I have found an additional item worth investigating. Some distance away, there is an opening in the side of a hill. This opening leads to a rock that seems to move when unobserved.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>102</ID>
		<ParentID>101</ParentID>
		<Text>
			NESIA: I would certainly like to study this mysterious stone! I struggle to imagine what may cause this sort of behavior.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>


	<!--NomaiText.Branch 2-->
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>201</ID>
		<ParentID>1</ParentID>
		<Text>
			SENNETTI: In light of the discoveries of the others, I have begun construction of a road to lead to both locations. It should help with navigating the… hazardous terrain.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>202</ID>
		<ParentID>201</ParentID>
		<Text>
			AZOLLA: Good idea Sennetti, we don’t want anyone to become lost with the constant heat of this planet.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<!--Ship log reveals go here-->
  <ShipLogConditions>
    <RevealFact>
      <FactID>HOT_PLANET_NO_CITY_FACT_FC</FactID>
      <Condition>1</Condition>
    </RevealFact>
  </ShipLogConditions>
  <ShipLogConditions>
    <RevealFact>
      <FactID>HOT_ROAD_FACT_FC</FactID>
      <Condition>202</Condition>
    </RevealFact>
  </ShipLogConditions>
  <ShipLogConditions>
    <RevealFact>
      <FactID>SIGNAL_LAB_RUMOR_FC</FactID>
      <Condition>3</Condition>
    </RevealFact>
  </ShipLogConditions>
  <ShipLogConditions>
    <RevealFact>
      <FactID>QUANTUM_CAVE_RUMOR_FC</FactID>
      <Condition>102</Condition>
    </RevealFact>
  </ShipLogConditions>
</NomaiObject>
