<NomaiObject xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/xen-42/outer-wilds-new-horizons/main/NewHorizons/Schemas/text_schema.xsd">

	<!--Main NomaiText.Branch-->
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>1</ID>
		<Text>
			SENNETTI: The Dree were not exaggerating, this area is quite hot. I will be quite relieved when we set up the portable life support.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>2</ID>
		<ParentID>1</ParentID>
		<Text>
			AZOLLA: I will as well, I fear we would not survive long in this heat otherwise.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>3</ID>
		<ParentID>2</ParentID>
		<Text>
			OKALIS: Hm, I don’t seem to be able to fire my portside thrusters, which is making maneuvering difficult.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>4</ID>
		<ParentID>3</ParentID>
		<Text>
			NESIA: I seem to have lost vertical thrust. I believe the excessive heat may be interfering with our propulsion systems. I would advise we retreat for the moment.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>5</ID>
		<ParentID>4</ParentID>
		<Text>
			OKALIS: …I actually seem to have lost all thrust, I may require assistance to return.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>6</ID>
		<ParentID>5</ParentID>
		<Text>
			AZOLLA: Unfortunately, that seems to be the case for all of us. It seems that we are trapped here, for the time being.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>7</ID>
		<ParentID>6</ParentID>
		<Text>
			SENNETTI: The temperature here is entirely inhospitable, if we are unable to find a way to propel ourselves soon, we aren't going to make it out!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>8</ID>
		<ParentID>7</ParentID>
		<Text>
			…
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>9</ID>
		<ParentID>8</ParentID>
		<Text>
			NESIA: Is the heat affecting my vision, or is there movement coming from the entrance?
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>10</ID>
		<ParentID>9</ParentID>
		<Text>
			OKALIS: There is! It seems the Dree have noticed our plight, and have come to retrieve us!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>11</ID>
		<ParentID>10</ParentID>
		<Text>
			DITYLUM: Hey, we noticed that you stopped moving, I thought you were going to go to the surface to set up life support?
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>12</ID>
		<ParentID>11</ParentID>
		<Text>
			AZOLLA: We were, but it appears our propulsion systems failed due to the heat.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>13</ID>
		<ParentID>12</ParentID>
		<Text>
			DITYLUM: We told you it was a bad idea to come far in here, weird signal or not. Come on, let’s get you out of here.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>14</ID>
		<ParentID>13</ParentID>
		<Text>
			AZOLLA: Thank you. Once you get us out of here, we should be entirely able to modify our propulsion systems to handle the heat, making our return trip much more successful.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>15</ID>
		<ParentID>14</ParentID>
		<Text>
			DITYLUM: Hah! And here I thought you couldn’t tell a joke without the science of it going over my head.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>16</ID>
		<ParentID>15</ParentID>
		<Text>
			…
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>17</ID>
		<ParentID>16</ParentID>
		<Text>
			DITYLUM: By the <![CDATA[<color=purple>Bramble</color>]]>, you’re serious aren’t you…
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<!--Ship log reveals go here-->
</NomaiObject>
