<NomaiObject xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/xen-42/outer-wilds-new-horizons/main/NewHorizons/Schemas/text_schema.xsd">

	<!--Main NomaiText.Branch-->
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>1</ID>
		<Text>
			OKALIS: Nesia, do you mind if I ask a potentially sensitive question? It's about Amylax and I, so I understand if your recent loss is still too sore. I ask because you are the only one of us who has any experience with relationships.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>2</ID>
		<ParentID>1</ParentID>
		<Text>
			NESIA: It is no problem at all, friend. What is your concern?
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>3</ID>
		<ParentID>2</ParentID>
		<Text>
			OKALIS: I don't know if it is a concern, or... well, I suppose it is a concern, though I struggle to think of any concrete foundation for it. It's just that, while everything seems to be going well between Amylax and I, I cannot help but worry.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>4</ID>
		<ParentID>3</ParentID>
		<Text>
			OKALIS: We are so fundamentally different, Nesia. Not in our interests, but on a very foundational level. We're different species, with different histories and customs, habits and-
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>5</ID>
		<ParentID>4</ParentID>
		<Text>
			NESIA: Slow down, Okalis, I'm a bit lost.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>6</ID>
		<ParentID>5</ParentID>
		<Text>
			OKALIS: Apologies. I suppose I simply have never heard of such a pairing, and fear that it may be something that fundamentally cannot work. Even the way our relationship began was, ultimately, the result of my failing to understand him and his customs. I'm just... worried.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>7</ID>
		<ParentID>6</ParentID>
		<Text>
			NESIA: Hm, I understand. If I may, however, I would argue your portrayal of the start of your relationship is inaccurate.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>8</ID>
		<ParentID>7</ParentID>
		<Text>
			OKALIS: What do you mean?
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>9</ID>
		<ParentID>8</ParentID>
		<Text>
			NESIA: You state that you <![CDATA[<i>]]>failed<![CDATA[</i>]]> to understand Amylax, but what I recall is you <![CDATA[<i>]]>struggled<![CDATA[</i>]]> to understand him. It is a somewhat small distinction, but I believe it is important here.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>10</ID>
		<ParentID>9</ParentID>
		<Text>
			NESIA: In particular, by struggling to understand him, you were ultimately successful, allowing your relationship to move forward. I hypothesize this will continue to be the case for the both of you, repeatedly struggling to come to an understanding, doing so, and moving forward together because of it. To be honest, it sounds similar to my relationship with Secca.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>11</ID>
		<ParentID>10</ParentID>
		<Text>
			OKALIS: How so?
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>12</ID>
		<ParentID>11</ParentID>
		<Text>
			NESIA: Secca and I had many moments where we struggled to come to an understanding. At the start of our relationship, we both thought ourselves quite clever, and it took some time to realize our interpretation of the other's words and actions were not always correct. Over time, we learned to do better, and to struggle to understand each other, as you and Amylax are doing. It took conscious effort to do so, but the mere fact that you came for advice shows you are already committing that effort.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>13</ID>
		<ParentID>12</ParentID>
		<Text>
			OKALIS: I... I suppose you are correct. We both care deeply for each other, and as you said, we have already proven that we can overcome the barriers of our differences. Thank you Nesia, you have been a great help.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>14</ID>
		<ParentID>13</ParentID>
		<Text>
			NESIA: I am glad. I have an open ear whenever you need to talk.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<!--Ship log reveals go here-->
  <ShipLogConditions>
    <RevealFact>
      <FactID>RELATIONSHIP_ADVICE_FACT_FC</FactID>
      <Condition>14</Condition>
    </RevealFact>
  </ShipLogConditions>
</NomaiObject>
