<NomaiObject xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/xen-42/outer-wilds-new-horizons/main/NewHorizons/Schemas/text_schema.xsd">

	<!--Main NomaiText.Branch-->
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>1</ID>
		<Text>
			DITYLUM: Hey, since you all have been working down here for so long, I thought I would come and let you know about a strange node I found the other day in <![CDATA[<color=orange>Briar’s Hollow</color>]]>. I tried to send one of those probes that you made in, but it seemed to lose signal immediately. I even tried tying a rope to one, but when I pulled on it the rope snapped, and I barely dodged the shrapnel from the destroyed probe.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>2</ID>
		<ParentID>1</ParentID>
		<Text>
			NESIA: Curious. Do you have any intuition as to why this may have occurred? Were there any strange marks on the recovered shrapnel?
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>3</ID>
		<ParentID>2</ParentID>
		<Text>
			DITYLUM: It almost looked like it had been destroyed by the rope itself, but I know I didn’t pull hard enough to cause that. I don’t know if I <![CDATA[<i>]]>could<![CDATA[</i>]]> pull hard enough to cause that!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>4</ID>
		<ParentID>3</ParentID>
		<Text>
			DITYLUM: Karenia’s really unnerved by it, she’s calling for the node to be destroyed using poison from the <![CDATA[<color=orange>Venomous Reject</color>]]>. Nobody can remember any story of such a node in all of our history, and nobody feels safe with it around.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>5</ID>
		<ParentID>4</ParentID>
		<Text>
			AZOLLA: Hm. It is not normally our nature to destroy something that could be studied, but if your people are so troubled by its presence, then we will do our best to eliminate the threat. We will simply have to make do with the other mysteries of the <![CDATA[<color=purple>Bramble</color>]]>.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>6</ID>
		<ParentID>5</ParentID>
		<Text>
			DITYLUM: Thanks, I’ll let Karenia know that you’ll take care of it.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<!--Ship log reveals go here-->
  <ShipLogConditions>
    <RevealFact>
      <FactID>DILATION_NODE_LOCATION_RUMOR_FC</FactID>
      <Condition>4</Condition>
    </RevealFact>
  </ShipLogConditions>
  <ShipLogConditions>
    <RevealFact>
      <FactID>DILATION_NODE_DESTRUCTION_RUMOR_FC</FactID>
      <Condition>6</Condition>
    </RevealFact>
  </ShipLogConditions>
</NomaiObject>
