<NomaiObject xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/xen-42/outer-wilds-new-horizons/main/NewHorizons/Schemas/text_schema.xsd">

	<!--Main NomaiText.Branch-->
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>1</ID>
		<Text>
			NESIA: Okay, after leaving the area through the opening we found near <![CDATA[<color=orange>Titan's Tears</color>]]>, we seem to have emerged into another large, open space. Okalis, can you verify the signals of our friends can be found within the node we just left?
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>2</ID>
		<ParentID>1</ParentID>
		<Text>
			OKALIS: Give me a moment… Yes, I can detect their signals coming from the knot we emerged from.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>3</ID>
		<ParentID>2</ParentID>
		<Text>
			NESIA: Excellent, that indicates that we should be able to retu-
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>4</ID>
		<ParentID>3</ParentID>
		<Text>
			OKALIS: My apologies for the interruption, Nesia, but I am also detecting their signals in that direction.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>5</ID>
		<ParentID>4</ParentID>
		<Text>
			NESIA: Interesting, do you suppose we have arrived in the same area that we previously left?
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>6</ID>
		<ParentID>5</ParentID>
		<Text>
			OKALIS: I suppose so. How exciting! Even seeing the spatial anomaly from when we first arrived, I never would have expected leaving this area may bring us directly back into it!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>7</ID>
		<ParentID>6</ParentID>
		<Text>
			NESIA: Suppose this node is recursive in some way? That would explain the curious signal I am detecting coming from it. If it truly is recursive, then this signal may simply be the ambience of this chamber, amplified through multiple passings through this node!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>8</ID>
		<ParentID>7</ParentID>
		<Text>
			OKALIS: I propose we inform the others of this immediately. A recursive node/dimension pair is certainly an important scientific discovery!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<!--Ship log reveals go here-->
</NomaiObject>
