<NomaiObject xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/xen-42/outer-wilds-new-horizons/main/NewHorizons/Schemas/text_schema.xsd">

	<!--Main NomaiText.Branch-->
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>1</ID>
		<Text>
			SENNETTI: As I’m working on these translations, I cannot help but become more and more fascinated by the Dree’s culture.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>2</ID>
		<ParentID>1</ParentID>
		<Text>
			SENNETTI: For one, the Dree seem to value scientific knowledge much less than us Nomai, instead pursuing more druidic practices. Most of these practices seem to center around the plant that surrounds us, which they simply call the <![CDATA[<color=purple>Bramble</color>]]>
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>3</ID>
		<ParentID>2</ParentID>
		<Text>
			OKALIS: Is this why many of their structures seem to be composed of these woody vines?
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>4</ID>
		<ParentID>3</ParentID>
		<Text>
			SENNETTI: Yes. Interestingly, the Dree seem to have some level of unexplained influence over the <![CDATA[<color=purple>Bramble</color>]]>. Rather than constructing buildings out of vines, as we previously assumed, it seems that they… <![CDATA[<i>]]>compel<![CDATA[</i>]]> the vines to grow into specific structures.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>5</ID>
		<ParentID>4</ParentID>
		<Text>
			SENNETTI: Even the planet they call home is only held together because the Dree willed the vines to do so.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>6</ID>
		<ParentID>5</ParentID>
		<Text>
			NESIA: How interesting! I look forward to being able to ask how exactly this ability works, and what else can be done with it!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>


	<!--NomaiText.Branch 1-->
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>101</ID>
		<ParentID>1</ParentID>
		<Text>
			NESIA: I had been wondering how our cultures might differ, but have been obviously unable to ask.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>


	<!--NomaiText.Branch 2-->
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>201</ID>
		<ParentID>2</ParentID>
		<Text>
			AZOLLA: I seem to recall they referred to it as the <![CDATA[<color=purple>Deep Bramble</color>]]>. Does my memory fail me?
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>202</ID>
		<ParentID>201</ParentID>
		<Text>
			SENNETTI: There is a small distinction to be made. The <![CDATA[<color=purple>Deep Bramble</color>]]> is the area we are in, while the plant itself is referred to as the <![CDATA[<color=purple>Bramble</color>]]>.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<!--Ship log reveals go here-->
</NomaiObject>
