<NomaiObject xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/xen-42/outer-wilds-new-horizons/main/NewHorizons/Schemas/text_schema.xsd">

	<!--Main NomaiText.Branch-->
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>1</ID>
		<Text>
			KARENIA: Okay, the <![CDATA[<color=purple>Bramble</color>]]> is primed, it’s now or never.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>2</ID>
		<ParentID>1</ParentID>
		<Text>
			AZOLLA: Ditylum has yet to  return from his task. Should we not wait for his assistance?
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>3</ID>
		<ParentID>2</ParentID>
		<Text>
			KARENIA: I would really like to, but I can’t guarantee how long the <![CDATA[<color=purple>Bramble</color>]]> is going to stay in this state. If we don’t do this now, we might never get another chance.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>4</ID>
		<ParentID>3</ParentID>
		<Text>
			AZOLLA: Very well then, I suppose we must proceed. Nesia, Sennetti, is the equipment in place?
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>5</ID>
		<ParentID>4</ParentID>
		<Text>
			NESIA: Everything is ready, the equipment should automatically supply nutrition to the node as the <![CDATA[<color=purple>Bramble</color>]]> grows it.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>6</ID>
		<ParentID>5</ParentID>
		<Text>
			AZOLLA: Excellent. Okalis, Amylax, you two are the visual and auditory organs of this operation. Notify everyone if anything seems amiss. Karenia, we are ready for you all to begin.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>7</ID>
		<ParentID>6</ParentID>
		<Text>
			KARENIA: Good. Okay everyone, follow my lead, try and guide the <![CDATA[<color=purple>Bramble</color>]]> to the <![CDATA[<color=orange>Eye</color>]]>.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>8</ID>
		<ParentID>7</ParentID>
		<Text>
			…
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>9</ID>
		<ParentID>8</ParentID>
		<Text>
			KARENIA: I think it’s working! The <![CDATA[<color=purple>Bramble</color>]]> is heeding our calls! I can feel it probing, searching for the source of the signal!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>10</ID>
		<ParentID>9</ParentID>
		<Text>
			AMYLAX: Something feels wrong, is the <![CDATA[<color=orange>Eye</color>]]> supposed to be big and hot? I swear that the <![CDATA[<color=purple>Bramble</color>]]> is focusing on something of that nature.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>11</ID>
		<ParentID>10</ParentID>
		<Text>
			OKALIS: Big and hot? No aspect of the <![CDATA[<color=orange>Eye</color>]]>’s signal suggests it should have either of those qualities. Unless… <![CDATA[<i>]]>a star!<![CDATA[</i>]]> Azolla! We need to shut off the project now! The <![CDATA[<color=purple>Bramble</color>]]> is attempting to grow the distant node in the core of a star!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>12</ID>
		<ParentID>11</ParentID>
		<Text>
			AZOLLA: No! Nesia, shut off the equipment! Everyone, direct the <![CDATA[<color=purple>Bramble</color>]]> away! We cannot allow it to-
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<!--Ship log reveals go here-->
</NomaiObject>
