<NomaiObject xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/xen-42/outer-wilds-new-horizons/main/NewHorizons/Schemas/text_schema.xsd">

	<!--Main Branch-->
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>1</ID>
		<Text>
			CURIOUSNOMAI: So, what exactly is our plan of escape? Do we try to fly out?
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>2</ID>
		<ParentID>1</ParentID>
		<Text>
			ANALYTICNOMAI: I fear that such a contemporary strategy may not work here, the <![CDATA[<color=orange>Vessel</color>]]> is registering very strange readings from the surrounding environment. It is possible that space does not function normally here.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>3</ID>
		<ParentID>2</ParentID>
		<Text>
			SPOOKEDNOMAI: What are we to do then? The warp core is damaged, so we can not simply warp out the <![CDATA[<color=orange>Vessel</color>]]>.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>4</ID>
		<ParentID>3</ParentID>
		<Text>
			CURIOUSNOMAI: ...Perhaps we still can. We have many smaller warp cores throughout the <![CDATA[<color=orange>Vessel</color>]]>, perhaps we can use a black hole core to escape.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>5</ID>
		<ParentID>4</ParentID>
		<Text>
			ANALYTICNOMAI: I do not believe that such an endeavor would succeed. A warp requires both a black and white hole, and we have no core with which to establish a white hole.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>6</ID>
		<ParentID>5</ParentID>
		<Text>
			CURIOUSNOMAI: I believe that it is still worth attempting, especially seeing as we currently do not have better ideas.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>7</ID>
		<ParentID>6</ParentID>
		<Text>
			ANALYTICNOMAI: I will concede that it is currently the best idea we have.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>8</ID>
		<ParentID>7</ParentID>
		<Text>
			NOMAILEADER: It is settled then, we will attempt to construct a makeshift warp device using one of the smaller black hole cores. I suggest that we do this in the lower bridge, as that area is both near the existing warp circuitry, and it should be easy to create a small area of artificial gravity down there so that we can work.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<!--Ship log reveals go here-->
  <ShipLogConditions>
    <RevealFact>
      <FactID>MAIN_BRIDGE_RECORDER_FACT</FactID>
      <Condition>8</Condition>
    </RevealFact>
  </ShipLogConditions>
</NomaiObject>
