<NomaiObject xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/xen-42/outer-wilds-new-horizons/main/NewHorizons/Schemas/text_schema.xsd">

	<!--Main NomaiText.Branch-->
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>1</ID>
		<Text>
			SENNETTI: This park appears to be the main social center for these people. I would greatly enjoy deciphering their language, but as it stands, I have nowhere to do my work nearby.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>2</ID>
		<ParentID>1</ParentID>
		<Text>
			OKALIS: I may have some positive news on that front, friend. The alien we first made contact with, assuming I am correctly interpreting their message, is directing us to set up a lab for just that purpose.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>3</ID>
		<ParentID>2</ParentID>
		<Text>
			SENNETTI: If that is true, then I am thrilled to hear it! Where are we being permitted to put this lab?
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>4</ID>
		<ParentID>3</ParentID>
		<Text>
			OKALIS: …That appears to be the catch. We seem to be intended to construct the lab in the area accessible through the knot currently over our heads, which has no bodies with significant gravity. Additionally, while I have been assured that it is quite harmless, there does seem to be some manner of beast in that area.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>5</ID>
		<ParentID>4</ParentID>
		<Text>
			SENNETTI: The lack-of-gravity issue, while frustrating, can be tolerated. As for the beast… if it means deciphering the language of these people, then I will be able to power through, regardless of how hideous it may be.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>6</ID>
		<ParentID>5</ParentID>
		<Text>
			NESIA: We all appreciate your courage in the pursuit of discovery, Sennetti. I believe I may be able to assist with your gravity issue. I have detected a strange signal in <![CDATA[<color=orange>Bramble’s Hollow</color>]]> that seems to be some manner of natural gravitational disturbance.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>7</ID>
		<ParentID>6</ParentID>
		<Text>
			AZOLLA: That is quite an interesting find, Nesia. Now that we are better oriented with our newfound friends, I propose you and I investigate that signal at once while Sennetti and Okalis begin constructing a translation lab. With the low visibility of this place, I suspect signals such as that will be highly valuable.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<!--Ship log reveals go here-->
  <ShipLogConditions>
    <RevealFact>
      <FactID>DREE_HOME_FACT_FC</FactID>
      <Condition>1</Condition>
    </RevealFact>
  </ShipLogConditions>
  <ShipLogConditions>
    <RevealFact>
      <FactID>PARK_LANGUAGE_LAB_FACT_FC</FactID>
      <Condition>4</Condition>
    </RevealFact>
  </ShipLogConditions>
  <ShipLogConditions>
    <RevealFact>
      <FactID>FOLLY_PARK_FACT_FC</FactID>
      <Condition>7</Condition>
    </RevealFact>
  </ShipLogConditions>
  <ShipLogConditions>
    <RevealFact>
      <FactID>LANGUAGE_LAB_RUMOR_FC</FactID>
      <Condition>4</Condition>
    </RevealFact>
  </ShipLogConditions>
  <ShipLogConditions>
    <RevealFact>
      <FactID>FOLLY_RUMOR_FC</FactID>
      <Condition>7</Condition>
    </RevealFact>
  </ShipLogConditions>
</NomaiObject>
