<NomaiObject xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/xen-42/outer-wilds-new-horizons/main/NewHorizons/Schemas/text_schema.xsd">

	<!--Main NomaiText.Branch-->
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>1</ID>
		<Text>
			SENNETTI: I have a troubling update, friends. It seems the main entrance to the <![CDATA[<color=orange>Venomous Reject</color>]]> has been killed off by the toxin in that area. To make matters worse, this has stranded Ditylum!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>2</ID>
		<ParentID>1</ParentID>
		<Text>
			OKALIS: Is there not another way there through the <![CDATA[<color=orange>Nursery</color>]]>? He should be able to simply drift through to return, correct?
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>3</ID>
		<ParentID>2</ParentID>
		<Text>
			NESIA: Unfortunately, the nutrient-rich fog of the <![CDATA[<color=orange>Nursery</color>]]> is quite thick, swiftly halting any movement that isn’t supported by a constant force.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>4</ID>
		<ParentID>3</ParentID>
		<Text>
			SENNETTI: I’ve spoken to the Dree about possible rescue methods, but they seem convinced all attempts would either fail or result in many deaths. When I spoke to them, they were already preparing for a period of mourning.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>5</ID>
		<ParentID>4</ParentID>
		<Text>
			AZOLLA: Friends, if the Dree do not believe it possible to save Ditylum, then it is up to us to do so. We cannot simply allow him to perish without attempting rescue, especially after how the Dree pulled us from the heat of <![CDATA[<color=orange>Magma’s Recursion</color>]]>.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>6</ID>
		<ParentID>5</ParentID>
		<Text>
			NESIA: Since our studies in this lab have already concluded, we can use the extra space to discuss various rescue methods.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>


	<!--NomaiText.Branch 1-->
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>101</ID>
		<ParentID>3</ParentID>
		<Text>
			OKALIS: Right, I remember the Dree cautioning us to be careful in there, as it would be easy for our thrusters to alert the fish.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>


	<!--NomaiText.Branch 2-->
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>201</ID>
		<ParentID>4</ParentID>
		<Text>
			NESIA: It pains me to think how the inability to rescue their friend must be hurting them.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
  
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>202</ID>
		<ParentID>201</ParentID>
		<Text>
			OKALIS: I struggle to understand how they could have given up hope so quickly.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>


	<!--NomaiText.Branch 4-->
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>401</ID>
		<ParentID>5</ParentID>
		<Text>
			SENNETTI: I agree. Ditylum came for us in our time of need, we must be willing to do the same for him.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
  
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>402</ID>
		<ParentID>401</ParentID>
		<Text>
			OKALIS: We will not rest until Ditylum is returned home.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<!--Ship log reveals go here-->
</NomaiObject>
