<NomaiObject xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/xen-42/outer-wilds-new-horizons/main/NewHorizons/Schemas/text_schema.xsd">

	<!--Main NomaiText.Branch-->
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>1</ID>
		<Text>
			OKALIS: Friends, I have spectacular news! Amylax has informed me there is a mysterious signal reverberating throughout the <![CDATA[<color=orange>Feedback Chamber</color>]]>, which arrived shortly before we did. I am certain it must be the signal from the <![CDATA[<color=orange>Eye</color>]]>!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>2</ID>
		<ParentID>1</ParentID>
		<Text>
			AZOLLA: Okalis, consider what you are saying for a moment. It seems highly implausible that the <![CDATA[<color=orange>Eye’s</color>]]> signal penetrated into the <![CDATA[<color=purple>Deep Bramble</color>]]>, and then became trapped in a particular area. How would that even occur?
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>3</ID>
		<ParentID>2</ParentID>
		<Text>
			OKALIS: I know that it seems implausible, but so does a signal older than the universe! It is what our clan risked everything to find in the first place. We would be disrespecting their sacrifice if we sit idle while a mysterious signal is well within our grasp!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>4</ID>
		<ParentID>3</ParentID>
		<Text>
			OKALIS: Please, look at yourselves. We are Nomai. We are meant to make discoveries, but we have been entirely idle for entirely too long. We <![CDATA[<i>]]>need<![CDATA[</i>]]> this.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>5</ID>
		<ParentID>4</ParentID>
		<Text>
			NESIA: …You’re correct, Okalis. As wounded as we may be, stagnating here will do us no good. Our friends would not have wanted us to stay here forever, refusing to move on.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>6</ID>
		<ParentID>5</ParentID>
		<Text>
			AZOLLA: Fair points, both of you. Alright, we will investigate this mysterious signal, but only if we unanimously agree to do so, understood?
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>


	<!--NomaiText.Branch 1-->
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>101</ID>
		<ParentID>1</ParentID>
		<Text>
			SENNETTI: With how our luck has been lately, Okalis, I have some trouble believing that.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>


	<!--NomaiText.Branch 2-->
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>201</ID>
		<ParentID>6</ParentID>
		<Text>
			SENNETTI: It will certainly be a risk, but I agree we should at least perform a cursory investigation.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>


	<!--NomaiText.Branch 3-->
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>301</ID>
		<ParentID>6</ParentID>
		<Text>
			OKALIS: Understood. Naturally, I agree we should investigate.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<!--Ship log reveals go here-->
  <ShipLogConditions>
    <RevealFact>
      <FactID>EYE_SIGNAL_RUMOR_FC</FactID>
      <Condition>6</Condition>
    </RevealFact>
  </ShipLogConditions>
  <ShipLogConditions>
    <RevealFact>
      <FactID>NOMAI_REVITALIZED_FACT_FC</FactID>
      <Condition>6</Condition>
    </RevealFact>
  </ShipLogConditions>
</NomaiObject>
