<NomaiObject xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/xen-42/outer-wilds-new-horizons/main/NewHorizons/Schemas/text_schema.xsd">

	<!--Main NomaiText.Branch-->
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>1</ID>
		<Text>
			SENNETTI: While Nesia heads the study of the Dree’s physiology, I would like to take the opportunity to share aspects of their culture that I learned of during my translation of their language.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>


	<!--NomaiText.Branch 1-->
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>101</ID>
		<ParentID>1</ParentID>
		<Text>
			SENNETTI: Rather than engaging in scientific pursuits, the Dree seem to have certain… influences over the <![CDATA[<color=purple>Bramble</color>]]>. This includes influencing the growth of the vines (as demonstrated by those holding together <![CDATA[<color=orange>Shattered Hearth</color>]]>) and even some level of communication with the plant.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>102</ID>
		<ParentID>101</ParentID>
		<Text>
			NESIA: Hypothesis: if they are able to communicate with the vines, they may be able to inform us what became of the launched escape pods.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>


	<!--NomaiText.Branch 2-->
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>201</ID>
		<ParentID>1</ParentID>
		<Text>
			OKALIS: Resuming our studies, the Dree seem to gain most of their nutrition from anglerfish eggs, domesticating and breeding the fish to do so.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>202</ID>
		<ParentID>201</ParentID>
		<Text>
			AZOLLA: Interesting. I wonder how they began this practice? I can’t imagine that anglerfish eggs would have been terribly easy for their ancestors to procure.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>203</ID>
		<ParentID>202</ParentID>
		<Text>
			SENNETTI: I believe I do actually have the answer to this question, as an old Dree story may explain it. The story is too long to transcribe here, but I had previously recorded it on <![CDATA[<color=orange>Magma’s Recursion</color>]]>.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>


	<!--NomaiText.Branch 3-->
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>301</ID>
		<ParentID>202</ParentID>
		<Text>
			NESIA: Agreed. Even now the Dree continue to keep lights on their homes to ward off any wandering fish.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>


	<!--NomaiText.Branch 4-->
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>401</ID>
		<ParentID>1</ParentID>
		<Text>
			NESIA: I have observed that the Dree seem rather… stagnant. They seem uninterested in exploring beyond their immediate vicinity and appear to have entirely accepted their current situation.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>402</ID>
		<ParentID>401</ParentID>
		<Text>
			OKALIS: I would agree, Nesia. We have also observed how this can be destructive, as they were unwilling to take the necessary risks to retrieve Ditylum when he became stranded at the <![CDATA[<color=orange>Venomous Reject</color>]]>, unable to cross the <![CDATA[<color=orange>Nursery</color>]]>.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>403</ID>
		<ParentID>402</ParentID>
		<Text>
			AZOLLA: Fortunately, that event seems to have changed their outlook considerably, as well as inspiring them to put more trust in us than they did previously.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<!--Ship log reveals go here-->
  <ShipLogConditions>
    <RevealFact>
      <FactID>DREE_STORY_RUMOR_FC</FactID>
      <Condition>203</Condition>
    </RevealFact>
  </ShipLogConditions>
  <ShipLogConditions>
    <RevealFact>
      <FactID>ALIEN_STUDY_DISCOVERY_FACT_FC</FactID>
      <Condition>1</Condition>
    </RevealFact>
  </ShipLogConditions>
  <ShipLogConditions>
    <RevealFact>
      <FactID>ALIEN_DRUIDCRAFT_FACT_FC</FactID>
      <Condition>102</Condition>
    </RevealFact>
  </ShipLogConditions>
  <ShipLogConditions>
    <RevealFact>
      <FactID>STRANDED_DREE_TEXT_FACT_FC</FactID>
      <Condition>403</Condition>
    </RevealFact>
  </ShipLogConditions>
  <ShipLogConditions>
    <RevealFact>
      <FactID>REJECT_EXISTENCE_RUMOR_FC</FactID>
      <Condition>403</Condition>
    </RevealFact>
  </ShipLogConditions>
</NomaiObject>
