<NomaiObject xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/xen-42/outer-wilds-new-horizons/main/NewHorizons/Schemas/text_schema.xsd">

	<!--Main NomaiText.Branch-->
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>1</ID>
		<Text>
			NESIA: What do you all suppose the <![CDATA[<color=orange>Eye of the Universe</color>]]> is meant to accomplish? Why did it call out to our clan?
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>


	<!--NomaiText.Branch 1-->
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>101</ID>
		<ParentID>1</ParentID>
		<Text>
			SENNETTI: The signal near <![CDATA[<color=orange>Magma's Recursion</color>]]>, unfortunately, sheds little light on this. Suppose the <![CDATA[<color=orange>Eye</color>]]> does not wish to inform us of its purpose?
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>102</ID>
		<ParentID>101</ParentID>
		<Text>
			OKALIS: How unsettling! I vote we explore other possibilities first, as the idea that the <![CDATA[<color=orange>Eye</color>]]> may purposefully be withholding information is frightening!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>


	<!--NomaiText.Branch 2-->
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>201</ID>
		<ParentID>1</ParentID>
		<Text>
			AZOLLA: Suppose the <![CDATA[<color=orange>Eye</color>]]> has no purpose at all? It may simply be a natural phenomenon that happens to emit a signal.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>202</ID>
		<ParentID>201</ParentID>
		<Text>
			NESIA: Perhaps, but the sudden arrival of the signal is rather odd, and Filix seemed to think the signal was significant. Additionally, I struggle to imagine how a purposeless, natural phenomena would be older than the universe.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>


	<!--NomaiText.Branch 3-->
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>301</ID>
		<ParentID>1</ParentID>
		<Text>
			NESIA: Suppose the <![CDATA[<color=orange>Eye</color>]]> is a construct left by some highly advanced species? It would explain the sudden arrival of the signal, as it may have some conditions that must be met before it will begin its call.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>302</ID>
		<ParentID>301</ParentID>
		<Text>
			OKALIS: Hypothesis: it may be a craft used to travel between universes! If a species used it to come here from an older universe, that might explain its apparent age!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<!--Ship log reveals go here-->
  <ShipLogConditions>
    <RevealFact>
      <FactID>EYE_PURPOSE_FACT_FC</FactID>
      <Condition>1</Condition>
    </RevealFact>
  </ShipLogConditions>
</NomaiObject>
