<NomaiObject xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/xen-42/outer-wilds-new-horizons/main/NewHorizons/Schemas/text_schema.xsd">

	<!--Main NomaiText.Branch-->
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>1</ID>
		<Text>
			NESIA: With our friend's language translated, we can begin assembling a better understanding of their physiology. I have erected this text wall to serve as a location for recording our findings.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>


	<!--NomaiText.Branch 1-->
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>101</ID>
		<ParentID>1</ParentID>
		<Text>
			OKALIS: Nesia, Azolla, and myself had the pleasure of attending an alien concert recently. We posited that they may have different vocal organs than us, allowing them to produce the otherworldly sounds we observed.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>102</ID>
		<ParentID>101</ParentID>
		<Text>
			SENNETTI: From what I've gathered, they have inhabited the <![CDATA[<color=purple>Deep Bramble</color>]]> in all of their stories, so it is very likely that they developed enhanced vocal organs as an adaptation to the environment.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>


	<!--NomaiText.Branch 2-->
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>201</ID>
		<ParentID>1</ParentID>
		<Text>
			NESIA: These aliens possess many adaptations that make them well-suited towards the environment of the <![CDATA[<color=purple>Deep Bramble</color>]]>. Most noteworthy is their sensitive hearing and the thin webs between their fingers and toes.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>202</ID>
		<ParentID>201</ParentID>
		<Text>
			AZOLLA: It should be noted that certain traits suggest they may originate from somewhere with more light, such as their shallow, likely vestigial eye sockets. Suppose they were not originally from the <![CDATA[<color=purple>Deep Bramble</color>]]>?
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>


	<!--NomaiText.Branch 3-->
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>301</ID>
		<ParentID>201</ParentID>
		<Text>
			SENNETTI: Especially impressive, their hearing even allows them to read by detecting the differences in sound reflecting off different textures. This seems to be why they write with such a thick, soft substance, and how they can read the chalky lines written by ourselves.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>302</ID>
		<ParentID>301</ParentID>
		<Text>
			OKALIS: It seems that this hearing is even sensitive enough to detect certain biological signals. Amylax seems to use my pulse to determine when I am tense or nervous. This may have helped them avoid predators in the past, such as the anglerfish.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>


	<!--NomaiText.Branch 4-->
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>401</ID>
		<ParentID>1</ParentID>
		<Text>
			SENNETTI: Our friends seem to navigate entirely through echolocation, emitting a high-pitched tone that they use to measure their distance to solid objects in their environment.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<TextBlock>
		<ID>402</ID>
		<ParentID>401</ParentID>
		<Text>
			AZOLLA: Notably, this tone is also outside of the hearing range of all but the youngest anglerfish, as we learned when Ditylum became trapped on the far side of the <![CDATA[<color=orange>Nursery</color>]]>, unable to return without his tone alerting the juvenile fish in that area.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<!--Ship log reveals go here-->
  <ShipLogConditions>
    <RevealFact>
      <FactID>ALIEN_STUDY_DISCOVERY_FACT_FC</FactID>
      <Condition>1</Condition>
    </RevealFact>
  </ShipLogConditions>
  <ShipLogConditions>
    <RevealFact>
      <FactID>ALIEN_SIGHT_FACT_FC</FactID>
      <Condition>201</Condition>
    </RevealFact>
  </ShipLogConditions>
</NomaiObject>
